boombah.com 2014-11-29

# Boombah Policies

Welcome to Boombah, Inc. (“Boombah”) website (“Site”). This Site is offered as a service to our customers. Boombah, it’s and affiliates and other members of our family of companies value your business and loyalty. We are committed to the protection of consumer privacy. Boombah has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate its commitment to the privacy and protection of your personal information. To better protect your privacy, Boombah provides this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## 1\. Personal Information Collection

Boombah may collect personal information like name, telephone number, email address, date of birth, home or business mailing address, and details regarding your mode of payment, e.g., credit/debit card or account information, when you access certain areas of the Site that require registration or payment for products and services, or if you require more information about those services.

At other times, Boombah may collect information that cannot be used to directly identify you, such as browser type, Internet Protocol (IP) address and similar non-personally identifiable information. For example, we may aggregate non-personal information about you and other customers who visit certain areas of our Site. Aggregated information will not contain any information that can be linked directly back to you. 

## 2\. How Boombah Collects Personal Information

Boombah may use any number of tools to collect information about you, your computer access points, and the web browser that you use to connect to our Site. For example, cookies are tiny text files that we place on your computer’s hard drive when you visit our Site. We may use cookies to personalize your Site experience. You do not have to accept our cookies and you may delete them after they have been placed on your hard drive. If you do not accept or delete our cookies, some areas of our Site that you access may take more time to work, or may not function properly. For more information about cookies, visit: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Boombah may also collect additional information from your web browser each time you visit our Site. We may collect information on the pages that you visit, the promotions or advertisements that you click on, and other actions that you take while using our Site. This information may include your IP address, the type of browser, the time that your browser was used to access our Site, and the referring website address.

Our Internet Service Providers (defined below) may also use other standard web-based technologies to analyze your movements while accessing our Site. The technologies include analytic solutions, web “beacons,” “pixel tags,” and “clear gifs.” These technologies help us ascertain the effectiveness of our product and service campaigns and marketing programs, allow us to customize the services offered on or through our Site, and help determine the best use for Site content, and product and service offerings. Some of this information, including the IP address, may be stored on our Internet service provider’s server logs, and may be available for extended periods of time. 

## 3\. Our Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Boombah uses the services of independent companies to provide certain services to you, including, without limitation, website hosting services, credit and debit card processing, reservations processing, and Internet connectivity services (“Internet Service Providers”). Boombah may share your personal information with the Internet Service Providers as appropriate. We do not share personally identifiable information with outside, non-affiliated third parties without your consent, except to the extent necessary to complete your request for services offered through this Site.

Boombah may use your personal information to contact you via mail, email, or telephone in order to give you updates about Boombah’s special events, new services, reservation confirmations, or other promotions that may be of interest to you. We also use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive from you. Your e-mail address will not be used for any other purpose or shared with outside third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We may also use your IP address to help protect Boombah and our Internet Service Providers from fraud.

Additional uses of your non-personal and personal information will allow us to tailor products and services specific to your needs, to help organize and manage your customer relationship and our business, to conduct business, to provide you with customer and guest support, to perform functions that are described to you at the time of collection, and to enforce our Site’s Terms and Conditions of Use.

We may also use non-personal aggregate information to improve our Site. For example, our Internet Service Providers may report to us that there were a particular number of visitors to a certain area of our Site, or that a certain number of men or a certain number of women completed our registration form in particular areas of our Site. Such information may also be used to analyze the effectiveness of our business and advertising models.

If you submit a resume or seek to fulfill other staffing requirements, we will use that information solely in connection with your application for current or future staffing requirements, and we may also share your resume or application information with our business partners or affiliates that have staffing requirements that you may be qualified for.

Boombah may also disclose your personal information as is necessary to: (a) comply with a subpoena or court order; (b) cooperate with law enforcement or other government agency; (c) establish or exercise our legal rights; (d) protect the property or safety of our company and employees, contractors, vendors, and suppliers; (e) defend against legal claims; (f) help with internal and external investigations; or (g) as otherwise required by law or permitted by law. We may disclose your information in connection with the sale or merger of Boombah or any transaction that involves the sale or assignment of some or all of our assets.

## 4\. Data Storage and Security

Boombah makes reasonable efforts to ensure that our Internet Service Providers have implemented physical, electronic, and procedural security measures to assist with safeguarding your personal information, and to help protect against unauthorized access and disclosure. Only our authorized personnel and our Internet Service Providers who perform legitimate business functions for Boombah are authorized to access your personal information. 

Notwithstanding our efforts, the Internet has inherent security risks. Boombah cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, personal searches, and other communications will always remain secure. You should take care with regard to how you handle and disclose your personal information or any username or password that you are required to use to access services on this Site. 

## 5\. Children and Data Collection

Boombah’s Site is a general audience Site. Boombah’s content is neither directed toward minors nor children who are under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If Boombah or its Internet Service Providers become aware that a minor or a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without the parental consent, that information will be deleted from our databases. Parents who have questions about personal information that may have been submitted by a child under the age of 13 should email us at [privacypolicy@boombah.com.](mailto:privacypolicy@boombah.com?subject=Children%20and%20Data%20Collection%20Inquiry)

## 6\. Your California Privacy Rights

Boombah will not share any personal information about you with outside third-parties for their direct marketing purposes to the extent prohibited by California law, unless you agree otherwise as authorized by your prior written consent. 

California residents have the right to request information from Boombah regarding the manner that we may share personal information with affiliated companies and third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To find out what and how we share such information, you may send us an e-mail request at [privacypolicy@Boombah.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boombah.com?subject=Inquiry%20About%20How%20Boombah%20Shares%20Information) or mail a request to: Privacy Officer, Boombah 202 Boombah Bvld, and receive the following information:

  * The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, if any;
  * The names and addresses of the third parties who received information for their direct marketing purposes; and 
  * Examples of the products and services subject to the third-parties’ direct marketing programs, if the nature of the third parties’ business cannot be determined from their names.

## 7\. How You May Access and Change the Information that Boombah Collects

The first time that you provide us with registration information through our Site, you may be offered the opportunity to subscribe to and receive additional information about our products and services. After your first use, you can change your initial choices by contacting our customer service e-mail at [privacypolicy@Boombah.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boombah.com?subject=Request%20to%20Change%20Email%20Subscription%20Settings). Each commercial e-mail that we send to you, will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of continuing to receive such messages. We may take up to 10 business days to process your opt-out requests. In some instances, we may have already shared your information with one of our authorized third parties before you changed your information preferences. In those cases, you may have to directly contact those third parties to opt-out of receiving their communications. 

FTC email compliance guidance allows us to send you transactional and relationship e-mails without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving those types of e-mails.

## 8\. General Information and Privacy Support Contact

Boombah may update this privacy policy from time to time, and you should take the time to review it each time that you visit our Site. If you require additional information about Boombah’s privacy commitment, please contact us at [privacypolicy@boombah.com](mailto:privacypolicy@boombah.com?subject=General%20Inquiry%20About%20Privacy%20Policy).
